# **COTY EADES**

Phone number and location available upon request

Coty.eades.dev@gmail.com

# **SUMMARY**

Motivated and experienced sales director with a strong background in retail management and customer service. Skilled in team building, inventory management, and employee supervision. Experienced in food health and safety, grocery store operations, and product placement / merchandising. Background experience in metal fabrication, machining, welding, warehouse procedures, and forklift operation. Currently pursuing a degree in Computer Science with a concentration in Programming / Software Design

# **SKILLS**

- Leadership C#
- Team Management Python
- Customer Service
  HTML, CSS, JS
- Inventory
  .NET API
- Food Health and Safety
  SQL
- SalesGraphQL
- Metal Fabrication / CNC Machine Operation
  Git

# **EXPERIENCE**

JANUARY 2022 - PRESENT

# SALES DIRECTOR, ALL ABOUT BLINDS – JOHNSON CITY, TN

Experience in implementing effective sales strategies, analyzing market trends, and identifying new business opportunities. Skilled at building and maintaining relationships with key clients, resulting in long-term partnerships and increased sales. Trained in measurement and installation of high-end window treatments such as blinds, shades, and shutters. Skilled at programming motorized smart shades and assisting customers with integrating them into their home IOT network. Responsible for building proposals based on clients needs, scheduling and workflow management of the installation / repair team. Responsible for maintaining company vehicles.

AUGUST 2020 - NOVEMBER 2021

## GROCERY DEPARTMENT MANAGER, EARTH FARE – JOHNSON CITY, TN /

### ASHEVILLE . NC

ī.

As the Grocery department Manager, I was in charge of accurately placing orders for incoming shipments while ensuring that the weekly purchase budget was not exceeded. Other responsibilities included quality control, reducing shrink / waste of product, and ensuring that all incoming product is scanned in and merchandised according to company policy. I was also responsible for leadership and training for a team of employees under my direct supervision. This included the dry grocery, dairy, frozen, and bulk food departments. Additionally, I am trained in merchandising and have traveled to other stores to assist in large resets and grand openings. I doubled as an Assistant Store Manager or Manager on Duty, overseeing the daily operations of the entire store and being cross trained in every department of the store. I participated in weekly corporate conference calls with the grocery category director and other members of senior management. I was called to return to this position upon the company reopening from their closure earlier in the year. I commuted for a few months to the Asheville location during the time frame that the Johnson City location was being remodeled to be reopened.

#### **FEBRUARY 2020 – AUGUST 2020**

## **PRODUCTION WORKER, SMILING HARA TEMPEH – BARNARDSVILLE, NC**

As a food production worker, I operated various industrial cooking appliances and manufacturing equipment to produce large batches of tempeh for sale to supermarkets and restaurants. I operated a forklift to load / unload shipments to and from distributor trucks. I took pride in maintaining the highest levels of cleanliness and food safety to ensure that all batches of tempeh had the best quality and were safe for consumption.

#### JUNE 2016 - MARCH 2020

# ASSISTANT GROCERY DEPARTMENT MANAGER, EARTH FARE – JOHNSON CITY, TN

As the Assistant Grocery Department Manager, I maintained the Dairy department. This included ordering all incoming product, managing shrink levels, merchandising product to the shelf, and following food safety protocols to ensure that all product was safe for consumption. I assisted the Grocery Manager with any tasks as needed. When the company closed due to bankruptcy in March 2020, I was tasked with assisting the liquidation company to execute all closure operations and product liquidation to maintain a smooth closure.

### **AUGUST 2012 – JUNE 2016**

## PRODUCE CLERK, FOOD CITY - PINEY FLATS, TN

As a Produce Clerk, I spent my time stocking produce shipments to the sales floor, cutting fruit and vegetables to create ready-to-eat arrangements, and maintaining the freshness level of the department by removing wilting or rotting products from the floor. I also assisted the department manager with orders and ensuring that the produce department was always wellstocked and presented in an attractive and appealing manner.

#### **AUGUST 2010 – AUGUST 2012**

# METAL FABRICATOR, INDUSTRIAL TOOL SERVICES - BRISTOL, VA

As a metal fabricator, I operated manual and CNC grinders, lathes, and mills. I fabricated metal using various welding, machining, and grinding methods to specific tolerances outlined on blueprints. I used a variety of measuring instruments such as dial calipers and micrometers to ensure tolerances were met. I also operated a forklift to load and unload trucks and relocate large machinery and materials. I utilized strong attention to detail to produce high-quality,

precise parts and products that meet or exceed specifications. I have experience in meeting very tight tolerances (+- .001) and worked with precision and efficiency.

2

# **EDUCATION**

2021 TO 2023 (CURRENTLY ENROLLED)

ASSOCIATE OF ARTS AND SCIENCES – A.A.S. COMPUTER INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY - CONCENTRATION IN PROGRAMMING, NORTHEAST STATE

**COMMUNITY COLLEGE** 

I am currently pursuing my A.A.S. degree in Computer information Technology. My expected graduation is May 2023. I am a member of the Honors Society. My plan is to continue in the future towards my Bachelor's in Computer Science.

2015 TO 2016

**TECHNICAL CERTIFICATION - ENTERTAINMENT TECHNOLOGY - LIVE SOUND AND AUDIO, NORTHEAST STATE COMMUNITY COLLEGE** 

# **REFERENCES**

Professional / Educational references available upon request.